he-equipment.com 2018-09-03

# H&E Equipment Services

PRIVACY POLICY 

H&E Equipment Services, Inc. , including any and all of its affiliates, parents, or subsidiaries (collectively “H&E”), is committed to reasonably protecting the personal and private information belonging to any and all visitors to their web-site. H&E promotes the use of fair information practices. Because H&E is committed to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices in the Privacy Policy below. This Privacy Policy outlines what H&E does with information that is collected by your use of this web-site [www.HE-Equipment.com](http://www.he-equipment.com/) (the “web-site”) and what measures H&E takes to ensure that your information is protected. 

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE 

When you visit the web-site, place an order through the web-site, request information or service through the web-site, or use the web-site to, among other things, request financing, or make employment inquiries, certain information and data about you and your location is provided to servers and databases maintained by H&E and its development partners. H&E and its partners utilize various commercial software and techniques to protect your information while you are using the web-site. 

While you do not need to register or provide personal information to use the web-site, your visit to the web-site does provide access to certain personal information such as your internet service provider address without you having to register. 

Registration may be necessary, however, to use certain aspects and services provided on the web-site, such as requests for parts, services, or equipment, requests for financing, or requests for employment or employment information, among other uses. Additionally, visitors with existing, established relationships and accounts with H&E may necessarily have to provide personal and account information to access certain aspects of the web-site specifically reserved to account holders. 

Any registration, personal, or account information that you provide to use these unique aspects of the web-site will be used by H&E to enhance your experience with our online presence, to personalize the service that you receive while visiting the web-site, and to make improvements to the web-site further streamlining and enhancing your experience. 

Through your use of the web-site, H&E may collect information from you including, but not limited to, your ISP address, domain names, or your e-mail address. H&E will not sell any such information without your authorization. H&E may, however, provide aggregate information to third parties regarding visitor data and information related to the web-site. 

H&E may also share your information with our partners and advertisers. H&E may send e-mails, mail, or other communications and correspondence to you about special offers or other information that H&E determines may be of interest to you. We may base such marketing, mailing, communication, and advertising decisions on information that we collect from you via your use of the web-site. H&E may also partner with or use outside, third-party companies for shipping, payment processing, or other services that are provided to you directly or are part of a larger service process that benefits you. We may, occasionally, share your private information with these third parties to the extent provision of such private information is necessary for the third party to provide service to you. 

Purchases, Requests for Quotes, or Requests for Service 

H&E may collect personal information as part of the process of providing you with a price quote for sale or rental of equipment or parts or for service. You may be asked to provide personal information including, but not limited to, your name, address, telephone number, location, and e-mail address. We may use this personal information to contact you, provide the quote, or to provide to you other information that you may have requested. 

Additionally, if you utilize the web-site to make a purchase, we may collect personal and financial information to complete the process. You may be asked to provide information including, but not limited to, your name, address, or personal financial information regarding income, assets, debts, or information related to or regarding credit-worthiness (including social security information or tax ID information). We may use this information to, among other things, complete purchase requests, respond to questions or inquiries, or address other issues related to your order. 

Financing 

You may consider financing certain transactions through use of the web-site. In the event that you choose to pursue financing, you may be asked to complete a financing application that will require submission of personal financial information regarding income, assets, debts, or information related to or regarding credit-worthiness (including social security information or tax ID information). H&E does not store or house this information on its web-site or any other web-site maintained, controlled, or owned by H&E.

Employment Inquiries 

You may consider reviewing employment information through use of the web-site. You may also consider applying for employment with H&E through use of the web-site. If you choose to submit an application through the web-site, you may be asked to provide certain personal or financial information – such as your name, address, e-mail, prior work history, educational background, or other personal, private information. H&E does not store or house this information on its web-site or any other web-site maintained, controlled or owned by H&E. Rather, the application process is completed via a web-portal and, upon completion, your information is transmitted via a secure connection to a third-party web-site maintained by Candidate Resources, Inc. (http://www.criw.com/). The privacy practices employed by Candidate Resources, Inc. govern the use of your information by this third party. H&E directs you to familiarize yourself with the privacy policies and terms of use that Candidate Resources, Inc. employs regarding your private information and data. 

Cookies 

When you visit the web-site, a piece of data called a cookie is stored on your hard drive. This cookie contains information about you and your browsing history or preferences. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. If you set your browser preferences to deny cookies from this web-site you may be denied access to certain functions and elements provided by the web-site. 

LINKS 

This web-site may contain links to other third-party web-sites over which H&E has no control. H&E is not responsible for the content of those linked web-sites or the privacy practices employed by the owners or those who maintain those linked web-sites. H&E encourages you to read the privacy statements and terms of use of these linked web-sites, which also collect your personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web-site. 

AUTHORIZED DISCLOSOURES 

We may disclose your private information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights or property; or (3) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of our employees, users of our products or services, or members of the public. 

COMMENTS 

Any comment that you may post or provide on this web-site or any linked web-site should be considered public. You should have no expectation of privacy in any such statement made, or in the manner in which you made such statement. Any and all such comments will become the property of H&E or any other entity exercising ownership and control of that web-site. 

CHILDREN POLICY 

The content of the web-site is appropriate for, but not targeted to, children under the age of thirteen. We do not market products or services to this age group. 

NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES 

If we decide to change the privacy policy, we will post those changes here so that you may always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

EFFECTIVE DATE 

This version of the policy is effective as of July 1, 2015.
